  // creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "19n+97=629; Whats n?",
    answer: "28",
    options: [
      "29",
      "56",
      "28",
      "15"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "42z-3=249; Whats z?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "7",
      "6",
      "12",
      "8"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "96+10m=466; whats m?",
    answer: "37",
    options: [
      "12",
      "27",
      "49",
      "37"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "974=26m+38; Whats m?",
    answer: "36",
    options: [
      "36",
      "28",
      "79",
      "18"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "59=-4976-53c; whats c?",
    answer: "-95",
    options: [
      "-120",
      "95",
      "-28",
      "-95"
    ]
  },
    
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "49x-3=-591; whats x?",
    answer: "-12",
    options: [
      "-12",
      "52",
      "-15",
      "17"
    ]
  },
    
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "20=-1708-96b; whats b?",
    answer: "-18",
    options: [
      "38",
      "-14",
      "-18",
      "20"
    ]
  },
    
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "46m+51=-4411; whats m?",
    answer: "-97",
    options: [
      "-100",
      "-97",
      "-57",
      "-98"
    ]
  },
    
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "87+85d=-6543; whats d?",
    answer: "-78",
    options: [
      "-45",
      "-92",
      "-17",
      "-78"
    ]
  },
    
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "-4892=78c+22; whats c?",
    answer: "-63",
    options: [
      "-63",
      "-57",
      "-98",
      "-28"
    ]
  },
    
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "44+19y=-1742; whats y?",
    answer: "-94",
    options: [
      "89",
      "37",
      "-94",
      "23"
    ]
  },
    
    
{

    numb: 12,

    question: " 60+63b=1320; what's b?",

    answer: "20",

    options: [

      "46",

      "14",

      "20",

      "34"

    ]

  },


    
    {

    numb: 13,

    question: "71=-337-8d; what's d?",

    answer: "51",

    options: [

      "25",

      "42",

      "39",

      "51"

    ]

  },
    
{

    numb: 14,

    question: "31y+58=2910; what's y?",

    answer: "92",

    options: [

      "92",

      "42",

      "79",

      "87"

    ]

  },
  
   {

    numb: 15,

    question: "75x-3=3297; what's x?",

    answer: "44",

    options: [

      "32",

      "27",

      "52",

      "44"

    ]
  },
    
    
    {

    numb: 16,

    question: "74+75a=-5176; what's a?",

    answer: "-70",

    options: [

      "62",

      "-54",

      "47",

      "-70"

    ]

  },
    
    
    {

    numb: 17,

    question: "92+10d=-138; what's d?",

    answer: "-23",

    options: [

      "-23",

      "14",

      "32",

      "-45"

    ]

  },
    
    {

    numb: 18,

    question: "92+10d=-138; what's d?",

    answer: "-23",

    options: [

      "-23",

      "14",

      "32",

      "-45"
    ]

  },
    
    {

    numb: 19,

    question: " -245-10n=85; what's n?",

    answer: "-33",

    options: [

      "-47",

      "14",

      "-33",

      "-65 "

    ]

  },
    
   {

    numb: 20,

    question: " 3118-82y=2; what's y?",

    answer: "38",

    options: [

      "43",

      "24",

      "38",

      "51"

    ]

  },
    
];